RIP-FIXES-SYNC
by VaVooM
♪ I'm dreaming
of a white Christmas... ♪
♪ Just like the ones
I used to know... ♪
Sarah darling, how are you?
Yes, I've heard
all about the opening.
This week?
No, no, it won't be a problem.
When are you planning
on coming for a fitting?
Today?
I'll get my best tailor on it.
Yes.
No!
Talk soon.
Brooke, stop what you're doing.
This is very important.
Yes?
Sarah Banks
is a Broadway producer
who's attending an opening.
She is a very demanding client,
and she's coming in today.
I need you to make
one of our new dresses work.
Got it.
I love the color,
but the dress feels
a little flashy for me.
Well, we could definitely
adjust the neckline.
And...
If we taper in the waistline,
it will give you
a more traditional silhouette.
Yes, that looks better.
Okay. Perfect.
And I will make sure
that I hem it...
so that it is perfect...
for your height.
You have a really good eye.
Thank you.
I'm hoping to become
a designer myself.
I'll just be glad
when the glitz
and glamour is over
and I get back to Bucks County
for the holidays.
I grew up right by there...
in Whispering Pines.
We're practically neighbors.
We are.
How's everything going?
I think this dress might work.
I said periwinkle,
not whatever that is.
The fitting went really well.
Good. Your next fitting
is at 3:00.
Is that a problem?
No. No, not at all.
I was just hoping that
maybe you would have some time
to take a look at
some of my sketches.
It would really mean
a lot to me.
- I'm chock-a-block right now.
- Chock-a?
Busy.
Oh. Okay.
Remind me later.
Okay...
thank you.
Is that it?
Oh, yeah. Sorry.
[♪♪♪]
[phone ringing]
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Not today.
Hello?
Hey, sweetie.
So I made a fruitcake,
and your father claims
he doesn't like it.
They're like
cherry-flavored bricks.
[Mom] And yet
he continues to eat it.
[laughs]
Only to amuse my wife.
I am so excited to see you guys.
[Mom] Oh, honey, we can't wait
to see you either...
and to meet Ethan.
You know, I think
you guys are
really going to like him.
He loves the holidays so much...
I call him "Mr. Christmas."
Oh, that is so sweet.
He sounds like a great guy.
I'm so excited that we're all
going to be together so soon.
And you know
I'm like a little kid
on Christmas morning...
only more excited.
Oh, honey.
Okay, well, listen, I love you.
- Love you, too.
- Love you.
Okay, bye.
- Love you, too.
- Aw!
[door entry buzzing]
[woman] Hey, come on up.
Okay, so it's not
your Christmas present, but...
Oh, you got the candle I like!
And...
And the wine glasses.
Yeah, I thought
you could use them
for your Friendsmas party.
Is that blazer
one of your designs?
Oh, yeah.
Nina is finally going to look
at some of my sketches today,
so I thought I would
give her a preview.
I was looking over
everything last night,
but I am so nervous.
Everyone wants cutting-edge.
When I was at
the Design Institute,
"classic" wasn't considered
a dirty word.
Well, I love your work.
Thank you.
I just feel like
I've been putting in
all of this effort,
and I'm still at square one.
Give yourself a break.
But, hey, on a lighter note,
Ethan is taking me for dinner
before your party tonight.
Oh!
Oh? He doesn't strike me
as the Santa type.
Well, it was a charity event
for his boss's wife.
Who knows...
Mr. Christmas
might just be the one.
[♪♪♪]
I can see the potential,
the attention to detail,
but this place
isn't ahead of the curve...
we define the curve.
Right...
That blazer you're wearing
is a Chanel throwback?
Actually, it's one of my own.
Style is informed
by celebrities these days.
There needs to be
a bigger impact.
Subtlety is a lost art.
You should rethink your designs.
Oh...
Okay.
Well, thank you for your time.
You know...
the history of fashion
shouldn't be ignored.
There's a lot to be learned
about the past
and how it shapes who we are
and what we wear.
Is that it?
Yes.
At least I stood my ground,
you know?
Told her what I really thought.
What about you?
How was your day?
The new client?
I roughed-out the plans
for the house,
which he approved.
That's great.
Why so glum?
We should be celebrating.
The thing is,
I'm going to be really busy
with this project.
Oh, how busy?
I can't get away
for the holidays.
Well, maybe just
for a couple of days.
Whispering Pines
is only two hours away.
It's not just about work.
Okay, well,
what else is it about?
Brooke, I think that
we're moving too fast.
Well, I appreciate your honesty,
but your timing
couldn't be worse.
It's too soon for me
to meet your family.
You know what that implies?
It implies a future,
which I gather you don't want.
I'm just not ready.
My career is taking off.
I'm going to be
traveling a lot...
Not to Whispering Pines with me.
I'm starting to feel like
this is more about you
having someone
to take home for the holidays
than it is about me.
I'm sorry, Brooke.
Brooke!
You don't have to rush off.
Merry Christmas, Ethan.
[♪♪♪]
[phone ringing]
[door entry buzzing]
It's a beautiful night,
isn't it?
Yeah.
I just love this time of year.
I get it.
The holidays
can be stressful sometimes.
They can be.
I'm going to a Friendsmas party.
Megan and Larry?
Yes!
Yes.
Well, I guess that
makes us friends.
I guess so.
Joel.
Brooke.
- Pleasure to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
So are you always this jolly?
It's a seasonal thing.
Yeah, I used to be that way.
What happened?
Don't ask.
Come on, cheer up.
It's a party.
[buzzer sounds]
[man] Come on up.
Ladies first.
Thank you.
It's the holidays, it's a party.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
It's just when you pour
everything into a career
that's not working
and your relationship fizzles
right before the holidays,
insecurity feels like
the only option.
Did you tell your mom
about Ethan?
No. Not yet.
So, anyway,
he walks into the audition,
nails it,
feedback has been great,
Okay, I still
have to read again.
After the holidays...
but I'm telling you
major buzz around town.
Okay, and I have to meet
with the director.
Yeah, it's a formality.
Listen to me,
this is no more bit parts,
no more commercials.
This could be
a major game-changer for you.
You are more excited
about this thing than I am.
Well, yes,
because I'm your agent.
- I get 15%.
- 10.
Okay, fine, I'll take
the rest in pride.
- Larry's the best.
- Yeah.
- [Joel] Hello again.
- Hi.
You having a good time?
Yeah.
I don't think
quite as much as you, though,
with your perpetual smile.
I'm an actor...
I'm always auditioning...
it's a professional hazard.
An actor, that's cool.
I am sorry that
I'm in such an un-merry mood.
Yeah, you said don't ask,
so I won't.
Career, relationship,
you name it.
Let's take it in order.
What do you do?
I'm a designer
with no immediate prospects,
hence my current employment
as an over-qualified tailor.
It's like that way with acting.
I've waited tables
just to pay rent.
And what about
your relationship?
My boyfriend... ex-boyfriend...
and I broke up a few hours ago.
Just in time for the holidays.
Oh! Wow.
There should be a law
against that...
no broken hearts
in December allowed.
So what is this part
you're up for?
Thank you.
Well, he's a guy
trying to get by
in a changing world.
Well, aren't we all?
Yeah, he's from a small town...
like, really small,
like the one in
"It's a Wonderful Life."
She's from a small town, too.
Whispering Pines, Pennsylvania.
Yeah. Everyone knows everyone.
Wow. I'm from the city,
you know, born and raised,
so it's a bit of a stretch,
but I can pull it off, right?
Yes, you can.
And, you know,
the character runs
his family's hardware store.
Oh, yeah.
My uncle runs the hardware store
in Whispering Pines.
- Seriously?
- Yeah.
Okay, hold on, wait a second.
You should got to this place
to get a feel
for small-town life.
That's a little overboard,
don't you think?
No, not at all.
The director loves authenticity.
He would be very impressed
if you did
that type of research.
He could be the boyfriend
you're bringing home
for the holidays.
Oh, no.
My parents
think that they're meeting
an architect named Ethan.
Wait a sec.
That's nothing.
Joel can pull off
being an architect.
He's an actor.
Watch this.
Ethan!
Ethan.
Ethan, Ethan, Ethan.
Hi. I'm Ethan the architect.
To Ethan the architect.
- Cheers.
It's not such a crazy idea.
Actually, it is.
It seems like a win-win to me.
I'm telling you,
this could be good for you.
The fact that
I am even considering this
is a little unnerving.
Is that my friend
or my agent talking?
Okay. Both, both.
Come on, B, take a chance.
It could be fate.
You know,
Brooke is a great girl.
[phone rings]
- It's my mom.
- Oh, okay.
Hi, Mom...
Hey, sweetheart.
When are you arriving?
Because I was thinking
we could all go for brunch,
and then, well, we'd meet Ethan.
You don't
have to sell me, Larry.
I'm... I'm intrigued.
You're nervous, aren't you,
about us meeting your boyfriend?
Okay, okay,
let's talk career, then, okay?
Honey, he is crazy about you,
he is crazy about Christmas,
so I like him already.
This audition matters,
all right?
A big part in a classy movie.
Brooke?
You owe it to yourself
to go the extra mile.
I'm sorry,
I know I'm going on and on,
but I'm just so excited.
I'm telling you,
Denzel would be halfway
to Whispering Pines by now.
I can't wait
for you to meet Ethan.
We'll be there tomorrow.
Okay, I love you.
Me too.
[Brooke] I can't believe
we're doing this.
[Joel] I know,
it's crazy, isn't it?
You know, I...
I don't get out
of the city much.
There's not a whole lot of cows
roaming around Manhattan.
I know.
You know, maybe...
maybe you should tell me
a little more about Ethan.
You know, he's an architect,
he's an athlete...
but, you know, what...
what makes him tick?
Apparently, it wasn't me.
Why did you break up?
I'm not entirely sure
that's relevant.
I'm an actor,
I like to know these things.
Well, in this scenario,
Ethan and I are still together.
[exhales]
[takes quick breaths in and out]
Sorry. I...
I get a little nervous
before a performance.
This isn't a performance.
This is my life.
Well, for me, it is.
I mean, you get to play you.
Look, things will work out
fine with your family.
They will buy me as Ethan
and their holidays
will remain intact.
You know what,
we're a little early.
Why don't we stop
and get a coffee?
Yeah.
[♪♪♪]
Whispering Pines
does not disappoint.
Yeah. It's pretty special.
Yeah, I didn't even know
towns like this existed.
It's like something
out of a Capra movie.
- Hmm?
- Frank Capra...
he did all those classics
about small-town America.
I mean, this is why
I want this role so bad.
It's about people
and how they relate.
Well, you're about to relate
to my entire family.
Well, my inner Ethan
is ready to roll.
- So, your mom is Donna.
- Yes.
Your dad is Walter.
What are they like?
Very sweet, very small-town.
They've been married
for 35 years
and they still hold hands.
Aw! That is so sweet.
What does your dad do?
Well, he had
a construction company,
he's retired now,
but he has
a very gruff exterior,
but he is all heart, so.
Sounds like my dad.
What about your family?
How come you don't spend
the holidays with them?
Well, my parents
are both actors,
so they're on the road,
doing a play.
- That sounds like fun.
- Yeah.
- Brooke...
- Hi!
Cheryl!
- I thought it was you.
- Hi!
It's so good to see you!
Oh, this is my boyfriend...
Ethan.
Ethan Reinhart.
Architect.
You look so familiar.
Is it your first time
in Whispering Pines?
Yes, yes, it is.
You know what,
and Brooke has told me
so much about it,
I'm finally going to get to meet
Walter and Diane...
Donna...
Walter and Donna.
Kidding.
- So funny.
- Joke.
He's constantly cracking me up.
It was great
to run into you, though.
Yes.
Very nice to meet you,
Ethan Reinhart, architect.
You got it.
The one and only.
I am so sorry.
I... I wasn't fully prepared,
and who is she?
- Oh, that's Cheryl.
- Oh.
Yeah. We went
to high school together
and we were friends...
which I say in the broadest
sense of the term.
Okay, well,
a bad dress rehearsal
means a great show.
You grew up here?
[Brooke] Home, sweet home.
I can't do this.
What are you doing?
Where is she going?
It's past the point
of no return.
Come on.
It's showtime.
Hello.
Sweetheart!
Sorry, I'm still getting
the hang of that auto park.
Oh, hi, sweetheart.
It's so good to see you.
And you must be Ethan.
It's so nice to meet you.
And so European.
This is my dad.
It's good to meet you, sir.
Well, I sure hope
you're both hungry
because I've made enough food
for an army.
Ooh!
Can I help you with the bags?
Oh, no, sir, I've got it.
- Walter.
- Ethan.
No, I mean
you can call me Walter.
Yes, sir, Walter it is.
You know,
I'm just really excited
that we're all home
for Christmas.
I mean, you're not home
for Christmas...
you're at our home
but our home...
I mean, their home...
And we are so excited
to be here.
This is... this is better
than I ever imagined.
Oh! Thank you.
Let's go in and eat!
Let's do it!
Thank you.
Ethan, do you have
any brothers or sisters?
Nope, nope, just me.
Brooke and Ashley
have always been so close.
Yeah, my big sister
is my role model.
She was the prom queen...
with the grace not to rub it in.
Well, that's a but much,
but I'll take it.
Ashley and I can't wait
for you to see the new house.
We're remodeling
the whole thing.
And as an architect,
I'm sure you can understand,
it is a total nightmare.
Oh, yes.
Yeah, it is taking forever.
We're still staying
with mom and dad.
[Walter grumbles]
Ethan, you'll bunk with Glen.
I'd love to get your opinion.
I'm okay with it
if you're okay with it.
- Hmm? What?
- Hmm?
Your opinion on the house.
I'd love to show you the plans,
get that expert point of view.
What were you...
What's going on with you, Tessa?
- I'm auditioning for a play.
- You are?
What's it about?
Family being together
at Christmas, just like us.
I really, really
want to play Emily.
I've been practicing
all the lines.
Well, hey, if you need
any help with that,
I'm your man.
Because...
I took theater in college.
Oh... uh-huh.
[text alert chimes]
Oh, shoot, I'm so sorry, guys.
I've gotta run to the office.
Oh, Glen.
It's 24/7 these days.
Not so fast, bub.
We still haven't finished
putting the lights up
on the roof.
Right.
Of course, the lights.
What was I thinking?
Maybe...
Maybe Ethan can help.
I'm sure he's got
a much better eye than I do.
Yeah, if you want
to put some lights up,
I'm your man.
Thank you, Ethan.
Well, come on.
This smells so good.
Let's eat.
Yes, please.
Just a head's up.
Walter can be
a tough nut to crack.
But keep cracking.
The funny thing is...
there's something
very familiar about you.
If I had a nickel
every time I've heard that.
Hey! Um...
how come there's not
a Christmas tree
in the living room?
It's only a week
until Christmas.
Because it's
the family Christmas tree,
and we decorate as a family.
Decorations,
tinsel, the lights...
- I can only imagine!
- Imagine?
- [Joel] What?
- What?
[laughing]
I'd better go do those dishes.
They're not going
to do themselves.
- Yeah, I'll go get the lights.
- Okay.
Hey, hey, hey...
How come my dad
thinks you look familiar?
I have a shaving cream
commercial running right now.
That's great, Jimmy Stewart.
How about we try
to stay in character?
Okay.
Oh, good luck with my dad.
[sighs]
Jimmy Stewart.
[Walter] Ethan!
Now, you've got to make sure
each light is clipped on tight.
Walter...
with all due respect, sir,
I'm an architect.
I've got this.
There.
There you go.
Architect, huh?
Ethan is wonderful, Brooke.
The way he just pitches in
and he helps your dad
with the lights.
And when he offered
to help Tessa.
I think Mr. Christmas
might be a keeper.
Yeah.
How's it going?
Good, good.
You know, I just...
I wanted to...
to give it some artistic flair,
make it original, right?
It's interesting.
[Walter grumbles]
I'm sure
it'll look better at night.
Anyway, I have some shopping
to do in town.
Do you want to come with me?
Yeah. Yeah, why not?
[Ethan laughs]
Yes!
This is exactly
what I was imagining
when I read the script.
Ah, all the actors that I admire
do this kind of research.
Becoming the character.
Okay, please just
don't be too intense
in front of my uncle.
He thinks you're my boyfriend.
Oh, hi, Brooke.
Hi.
This must be Ethan.
[laughs]
Uncle Hank.
All right.
Wow. How long
have you had this place?
It was my dad's,
and my brother, Walter,
went into construction,
but we grew up in this place.
That is-that is...
That is perfect.
It is if you like hardware.
Such a wonderful feel.
I can... rrrr... sense the history.
I think you need
to get out of the city more.
[laughs]
Yeah, well,
I keep telling him that,
but Ethan is just
such a die-hard New Yorker.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, excuse me.
I'll be right back.
Hey...
I really need you to be
a little bit more subtle.
Okay? This is
a regular hardware store.
No gushing over
the hammers and nails.
Okay. I am a method actor.
That's good for you,
but I really need you
to take this seriously.
I got it.
Okay.
I'm just going
to go do some shopping.
- All right.
- Okay.
Bye.
That's my girl.
So, Hank, let's talk tools.
Do you sell Christmas trees?
I do.
Uh, I want the biggest...
the biggest, greenest one
you've got.
I'm in town for the holidays,
it's a gift for the hosts.
I have a real nice one
right over here.
Oh, uh, no, no.
I mean... big.
How big?
Surprise!
I got a tree.
A family tree?
Uh-huh.
Well, normally,
we do this together,
it's a bit
of a family tradition,
but... but thank you!
I mean, this is...
so nice.
Will it even fit in the door?
I got the biggest one
on the lot.
Yeah, maybe even
the biggest one in the state.
Glen.
We've got some work to do.
I am pulling, Walter.
- You call that pulling?
- I'm pulling!
- Put your back into it.
[♪♪♪]
We are going to need
a bigger tree stand.
Yeah. Or a bigger house.
Well, why don't we just
have dinner,
and then we can figure
this all out tomorrow.
It's the prettiest tree
I ever saw.
[adults laughing]
Want to help Grandma
make dinner?
- Yes.
- Come on.
I know you meant well.
I got so excited.
This is my first tree.
You've never had
a Christmas tree?
Well, not until now...
I'm Jewish.
Oh...
Okay...
Uh, why didn't you tell me?
Well, I didn't think
it was relevant.
No, normally, it wouldn't be.
However, we came here
to celebrate Christmas
with my family,
who loves Christmas.
They think you're Ethan.
They think
Ethan loves Christmas.
[Walter] Brooke!
It's going to be all right.
My family thinks
Ethan is Mr. Christmas!
Okay, that might be a problem.
Just a little one.
But, hey, it's a point
for your performance.
I still think
I can pull this off.
Okay.
How?
Well, I've never
celebrated Christmas before,
but I always wanted to.
You know, the perfect
storybook version, right?
Decorate the tree,
the stockings on the mantel,
Christmas cookies, candy canes,
sleigh rides...
all the fun stuff!
It always seemed so great to me!
It is fun.
When it's not too complicated.
It's a holiday, let's enjoy it.
What could go wrong?
[Donna] I hope you like ham!
I've never had ham.
That's an interesting
plot twist.
Emily is really strong.
She refuses to give up.
Okay.
You've got this.
What if I forget my lines?
[Joel] Don't worry
about your lines.
You know what, use the script
as sort of a loose guideline.
Say what you feel.
[director clears throat]
Actually, I spent
the last six months of my life
working on this,
so I'd appreciate it
if you stuck to the lines.
Tessa, are you ready?
Writers.
Go get 'em.
You're so good with her.
Well, she's a great kid.
Emily, what are you doing?
I'm making you
a Christmas present.
A special, magical,
wonderful one.
I can't wait to see it.
[Tessa]
Not until Christmas morning.
You promise you're coming home?
I promise.
- Great job.
- Thank you.
Thank you very much.
[whispers]
There's other people here.
You were great.
She is fantastic.
I know, I'm just nervous.
Auntie Brooke!
Yeah?
I get to play Emily.
Mazel tov!
What?
Congratulations.
I'm so proud of you.
Thanks for all the help, Ethan.
My pleasure.
- I need to ask a favor.
- Okay.
My wife was doing
the costumes for the play,
but she got a terrible flu.
I was hoping you could help out.
Okay, well, what kind
of costumes do you need?
It's a period piece, the 1920s.
I don't know, Roger.
That's a pretty tall order.
We're really in a bind.
I'll do what I can.
Thanks!
I'm just feeling
a little overwhelmed.
You look so familiar.
Have we ever met?
What kind of shaving cream
do you use?
I realized I haven't properly
introduced you two.
Roger and I went
to high school together,
and Ethan is an architect
from New York.
- Nice to meet you.
- You as well.
I'm an architect.
[Roger] Well, I'd better
get back to work.
I can't thank you enough.
That smile
is all the thanks I need.
- Hey.
- Hi.
I thought I'd do
a little baking.
- Oh.
- Ooh.
- Maybe...
- What?
Any chance
of a gingerbread house?
Now, that is a wonderful idea.
I haven't made one of those
in years.
And we have an architect
who can design it.
I am more of
a brick-and-mortar guy.
But I'd love to.
Good.
You are such a delight
to have here!
Okay...
All right, I will show you mine,
but you have to show me
yours first.
Okay.
Wow. You are an artist.
Thank you.
Ta-dah!
You are...
an actor.
It's just a little bit boxy.
Well, it's my first
gingerbread house, you know?
I'm not an architect,
I'm an actor playing a role.
So why did you become an actor?
It's the family business.
Fortunately for me,
I absolutely love it.
So I take it you've played
all kinds of roles?
Oh, yes.
Everything from Shakespeare
to commercials.
But Mr. Christmas
is by far the most fun.
I am really glad I'm here.
[Donna] Hello!
Mom.
I hope I'm not interrupting...
No.
I made some icing
for the trim and the roof.
Ah!
Mr. Christmas?
Oh, why, thank you.
- Mm!
- Mm-hmm?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah?
Let's get baking!
I'm just wondering
if we should move the chimney.
- How's that?
- Looks good.
Okay.
Well, that's
a very unusual design.
Well, Ethan wanted it
to be an original, so.
Well, it's original, all right.
Edible roofs can be
extremely complicated.
Yeah, and Ethan's ideas,
I mean, they are...
big concepts.
You know, big ideas.
Real big.
You are doing
such a good performance,
we might actually
get away with this.
You sure there's nothing
I can do to help?
Oh, I'm positive.
Just relax.
Later, we're going
to decorate the tree.
Dinner was great, Mom.
[Donna] Oh, thanks, sweetheart.
[Walter]
It was wonderful, darling.
Hey, look,
the gingerbread house is done.
I don't think
gingerbread is his medium.
[Walter grumbles]
Where is Ethan anyway?
I thought I'd get a head start,
and I am having a ball!
You're decorating
the family tree.
How's it look?
Good, but, it's just...
it's supposed to be
for the whole family,
right, Wally?
- Walter.
- Yep.
Normally, we all do it.
But we can all just start again.
Walter, come in the kitchen
and help me.
[Walter grumbles]
I'm so glad
I'm not the new guy anymore.
I was just trying to help.
I know.
[commercial] For the best
in men's grooming products,
you've never had a shave
as close as this.
[Joel] Wait for it.
So smooth!
Okay, you know
what's not so smooth?
You just ate all the popcorn.
No. It was really, really good.
I usually like it with butter,
but this is delicious.
Yes, delicious.
That's the popcorn
we usually use
to string on the Christmas tree.
I am so sorry.
I didn't realize.
It's okay.
[laughs]
- [Ashley] Glen!
- Yup!
Your family thinks
I am really bad at Christmas
and they have no idea why.
Maybe we should tell them.
That you're not my boyfriend?
That I'm Jewish.
You don't have to be
any particular religion
to decorate a tree,
or feel a sense of goodwill,
or make
a lopsided gingerbread house.
Look, Ethan has nothing on me
except a little bit of practice.
I really hope
you're not acting right now.
Ethan.
This is my favorite tradition.
Gathered around the piano,
singing Christmas carols
with my family.
Just me and my girls.
Do you sing?
Um...
yeah, I can...
I can carry a tune.
[playing beginning notes
of "Deck the Halls"]
♪ Deck the halls
with boughs of holly ♪
♪ Fa la la la la
la la la la ♪
♪ 'Tis the season
to be jolly ♪
♪ Fa la la la la
la la la la ♪
Ethan!
You don't know the song?
"Deck the Halls."
You didn't sing
Christmas carols as a kid?
No, but I always wanted to.
Your parents just
weren't into it, or?
Well, they...
they sang other songs.
What do you mean?
I'm Jewish.
Oh!
Mr. Christmas is Jewish?
He's Jewish.
Yes, he is.
Yes. Yes...
I...
I kept telling Brooke
how excited I was to come here
and celebrate Christmas
for the first time with you all,
so she gave me the nickname.
It's...
It's been more fun
than I ever imagined.
Oh, I hope so.
I just wanted you
to feel at home.
Oh, you have.
You do.
That's cool.
So you celebrate Hanukkah?
Yeah, that's right.
Maybe we could celebrate
both holidays.
That is the best idea ever.
You know, maybe you can
teach me some songs,
and I can teach you a few.
Yeah.
Hey, Dad?
It's...
it's time to light our tree.
Ethan?
Would you like to do the honors?
I would love that.
Three, two, one...
[click]
[Walter grumbles]
[laughing]
After we dropped Tessa off
at the theater,
we stopped by the deli
and got some bagels and lox.
Nice!
Wow, that looks delicious.
Question...
when exactly is Hanukkah?
It starts in two days.
Which is
three days before Christmas.
That's right,
and that is
a lot of celebrating.
And I'm making a Hanukkah list
of all the things
I still need to get.
Always with the lists.
You know, we have been in a rut,
and now that Ethan is here,
he's just brought the life
right back into the holidays.
Wow.
Hey, we were hoping
that we could
maybe swing by our new place.
We'd love to get
your professional opinion.
We want to build a portico,
we're not sure.
A portico?
[Glen and Ashley] Yeah.
You know what, actually,
I needed to go get some fabric
for some of the costumes,
and Ethan...
Ethan was going to help me, so.
Yeah.
Well, just for a few minutes.
And you want to see
the house, right?
Mm-hmm.
All right, home, sweet home.
This is it.
So, Ethan, do you think
a portico would work
over the back door?
Yeah, sure.
I don't see why not.
It's, um...
They just started work
on the kitchen,
so you're going to kind of
have to use your imagination.
Yeah.
Oh, and we wanted to put in
a bay window somewhere.
Any ideas?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, sure.
How about here?
You can't put it there.
Huh?
It's a bearing wall.
I'm just thinking out loud,
it's part of my process.
I just draw them,
I don't build them.
Right.
Oh, hey, what do you think
of the gables?
I'm on the fence
about the gables.
You know what,
why don't we go
check out upstairs, yeah?
[Glen] Yeah, it's just...
How does an architect
not understand structure?
I think you just
make him nervous, Dad.
Yeah, I guess.
[♪♪♪]
Larry called while I was
at the hardware store.
There are only five actors
in contention for the role.
- That's amazing.
- Yeah.
Your uncle thinks
I'm a little weird,
but I'm starting to fit in.
What are these?
Oh, um...
well, this is for Tessa...
or Emily.
And this one is for
Emily's mother.
These are amazing.
Thank you.
Wow, um...
Did you always
want to be a designer?
Mm-hmm.
Always.
I saw Cinderella
when I was a little kid,
and for me,
it was all about the dress.
I ran home,
and I made a ball gown.
There was so much
satin and tulle,
and I wore it for a week.
[laughing]
I was the same way about acting.
I mean, you wore the dress,
I carried the sword.
I was a seven-year-old
swashbuckler.
You have a really pretty smile.
Thank you.
I seem to be growing
into this role.
Yeah, that's good.
I think...
I guess.
I find you very confusing.
Yeah, so is this situation.
Yeah, well,
I'm as confused as you are.
I'm going to go get
some hot chocolate.
Can I get you anything?
No, I'm good.
Thanks.
[football playing on TV]
Look at you,
you've got the game on.
Are you enjoying yourself?
Yeah, yeah.
I could sure see it better
if these glasses
weren't so dirty.
Here, let me
give you a hand with those.
I love props.
Props?
Glasses.
Every season, every sport,
I always root for the home team.
Phillies, Eagles, 76ers...
[commercial] For the best
in men's grooming products...
Ah, thank you.
You've never had a shave
as close as this.
Here you... here you are.
So smooth.
The Christmas Bowl
is brought to you
by All-Natural.
[Walter] What's so smooth?
You, sir.
So smooth.
What?
I only made one wish this year...
for all of us
to be together again.
And scene.
You were wonderful.
You know, you and Emily
have a lot in common.
Why don't you try to pretend
you're talking
to your own family?
Maybe I could be
an actress someday.
Well, you already are.
You just keep on doing
what you're doing
and the audience
will believe everything.
If you feel it, so will they.
She really likes you.
I just have to get something
for one of the costumes.
Yeah, I...
I have some shopping
to do in town.
Maybe I'll bump into you.
Right, okay.
Well, I should get going.
You like her, too?
Yes. Yes, I do.
Have you got her a gift yet?
That is next.
But first,
let's get
these acting exercises.
Try to do as I do.
Ready?
[trilling]
[Walter grumbles]
Where were we?
I'm looking for
a slip to go underneath
a costume that I'm making.
We have several that might work.
It's probably about
that length and fullness.
Okay.
Wow.
That is a beautiful dress.
Are you married?
Not yet.
When you get married,
you know where to come.
[chuckles]
I guess so.
- They're over here.
- Perfect.
Thanks again.
Uh, so, Brooke goes into
a bridal shop...
And then he just...
Maybe he bought her a ring.
Holy Hanukkah!
We've got to tell Mom and Dad.
Yeah, this is big.
[Donna shrieks joyfully]
I don't think we're supposed
to know about this yet...
but Ethan and Brooke
are engaged.
They're engaged?
Why do you sound so surprised?
They've been dating
for six months.
That's how long
it took you to propose to me.
Yeah, but...
all right,
he seems nice enough...
but there's just something
that just isn't right.
He's a bit of an odd duck.
What on earth does that mean?
I can't quite
put my finger on it.
Walter...
we have to let her go.
Why hasn't she said
anything to us?
Probably because she knows
her father isn't ready.
You...
You have to watch
your cholesterol.
[grumbles]
[Joel] Careful.
[Brooke]
Can you tell me what it is?
Just wait.
You're gonna love this.
- Oh, gosh. Okay.
- A little more.
Mm-hmm.
A little bit more.
- Mm-hmm.
- And stop.
- Okay.
- Surprise!
Wow.
I think he's bigger
than the tree.
Yeah!
You really are growing
into the role of Mr. Christmas.
I told you I could do it.
You know, this town is just...
so inspiring.
Thank you.
For doing this.
It's my pleasure.
Everything about
Whispering Pines is...
...it's magical.
[chuckles]
We should get inside.
[Brooke] Mom? Dad?
Uh...
Hi.
Is there something
you want to tell us?
- What do you mean?
- There's no use denying it.
We already know.
You do?
Mm-hmm.
I'm so sorry.
I wanted to tell you
so many times.
Yeah, so did I.
It's all right.
- It is?
- Yes.
You are engaged
and we could not be happier!
I hope you didn't want
to keep it a secret.
Yeah, no chance.
Word travels fast
in this family.
Yeah.
You need to tell me
everything about your dress.
Can I be a flower girl?
Okay... yes.
Did you plan a date?
Because we have to book
the venue.
We've got flowers...
Do you want a singer?
I was thinking a Hawaiian theme.
You take good care
of my little girl.
Yes, sir.
Two words... bachelor party.
Right?
[Walter grumbles]
I have no idea
what to tell my family,
or how?
And now they think
we're engaged,
that makes this even harder.
How do we ever reverse course
from this point?
I don't know.
I don't want to ruin
anybody's Christmas...
including my own.
Yeah, and now my mom
is really excited
about celebrating Hanukkah, too.
We have to keep
the performance going.
It is the same storyline...
with an unexpected twist.
Yeah...
Hi, Mom.
Oh! Look at you two,
holding hands on the loveseat,
just like me and your dad.
So, what do you think of this?
I made it myself.
I found all of these
fabulous Hanukkah
arts and crafts online.
That sounds like a lot of fun.
Oh, it is!
And I've only just begun.
She has a glue gun.
Can I get a ginger tea
and a coffee?
Yes.
Thank you so much.
You know, all anyone wants
to talk about is you and me.
Oh, yes, I know.
I was... I was hiding out
in the hardware store,
and your dad came in
and told Hank we were engaged.
Oh, great.
How are we ever
going to get out of this?
Well, we let some time go by,
say things didn't work out,
and we'll break up.
Ooh! Don't tell your parents
it was me.
I don't want them
to be mad at me.
I wouldn't worry.
They love you.
They love Ethan.
They don't know Ethan.
It's you they love.
- Thank you.
Yeah, well, you know...
I like them, too.
A lot.
And sometimes,
I wish this were real.
Brooke!
Oh, hi, Cheryl.
I hear that you guys
are engaged?
- Yes.
- Yeah.
Congratulations.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
I want to get a picture
of you guys.
Hashtag my former bestie
with her fiance.
You know, we should probably
get going.
I have, like,
a million presents to wrap.
Yes, so many presents.
Okay, well, I better be invited
to the wedding.
[Brooke] You got it.
Hashtag Ethan Reinhart.
Hashtag unbelievable.
These costumes are amazing.
Thank you.
Would you mind
trying on this jacket for me?
I just need to fix the collar.
Sure.
Oh, well, you're definitely
taller than Roger,
but how does it feel?
It's a perfect fit.
[rustling]
Wow. Look at you.
Well, Emily's father
is a soldier.
- [cell phone ringing]
- Oh, sorry.
[Donna] Try one of these.
Hello?
Hey, Brooke.
I got tagged in a photo...
apparently, you and I
are supposed to be engaged.
Thank you for letting me know.
It's a photo
of you and another guy...
but it's my name.
That is very interesting.
As far as I know, we broke up.
That is a very good point.
That's all you have to say?
Is it possible
for us to discuss this
after the holidays?
Well, I'd like
to discuss it now.
No, no, no. I'm sorry,
that won't be possible.
Thank you so much for calling.
[Donna] Who was that?
Just a designer who was
looking for an assistant,
but I'm past that.
These snacks look good.
♪ We wish you
a Merry Christmas... ♪
a Merry Christmas ♪
♪ We wish you
a Merry Christmas... ♪
♪ And a happy Hanukkah ♪
Ethan, I have something for you.
It's early...
- [Joel] Wow!
- But I couldn't wait.
Mom...
Wow...
Good start.
[laughing]
"Thank you for sharing
the holidays with us...
Love, The Millers."
What is it?
A menorah.
What's that?
Well, this is for celebrating
the eight days of Hanukkah.
We light a candle every night.
Can I light one?
Not until tomorrow.
That's because tomorrow
is the first night of Hanukkah,
and then three days later...
Christmas.
You know,
as crazy family holidays go,
this one's pretty great.
You're right again, Walter.
You're right again.
Here you go.
Oh, thank you.
This is a very messy...
and delicious change of pace.
Thank you.
How come you make
jelly doughnuts?
Well, the oil
that we fry them in
represents
the Miracle of the Oil.
That's because there was
only a tiny amount of oil
in the temple,
but it lasted
for eight nights...
The same as Hanukkah.
So what are these?
- Sufganiyot.
- What he said.
- Have one, you'll love them.
All right, let's do it.
After you, Walter.
Sufganiyot.
- Mm.
- Oh, wow.
Okay...
I'm sold.
Hanukkah tastes
just as good as Christmas.
I used to love these
when I was a boy.
You have a little on you.
Yeah.
Where did you grow up?
- In...
- New Haven, Connecticut.
And does your family live there?
Yes...
yes, they do.
They must be
awfully proud of you.
This is how the holidays
ought to be,
all of us here together.
- Ethan.
- Hmm?
Can you teach us a another song?
- That's a great idea.
- Yeah.
Of course, I can.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
♪ Oh, Hanukkah, Oh, Hanukkah
Come light the menorah ♪
Come on,
what are you guys doing?
♪ Oh, Hanukkah, Oh, Hanukkah
Come light the menorah ♪
♪ Let's have a party ♪
♪ We'll all dance the hora ♪
- ♪ We'll all dance the hora ♪
- [doorbell rings]
- Again, again.
- [knocking on door]
♪ Oh, Hanukkah, Oh, Hanukkah
Come light the menorah ♪
[door opens]
[Ethan] Excuse me.
♪ Let's have a party ♪
- Excuse me.
- ♪ We'll all dance the hora ♪
Hey.
I was knocking.
No one answered.
Can I help you?
Yes. Who are you?
I'm Ethan.
Who are you?
Ethan.
Oh, there's two Ethans!
I didn't think you were
going to be able to make it.
Everyone, this is Ethan.
We went
to fashion school together,
and he is here
visiting his family
in Harrisburg.
I know you're really busy,
but I'd love to catch up.
Ethan, can I get you
some eggnog?
- Yes, please.
- No, thanks.
It's very confusing
having two Ethans in my life.
Yeah, I'll bet.
You know,
but now they get to meet, so.
I've heard
so much about you, Ethan.
I wish I could say the same.
I have to go into town
to get some fabric.
Maybe we could stop
and have lunch?
We have so much to talk about.
We certainly do.
Thank you.
Nice meeting you, Ethan.
Bye.
It was nice to meet you.
Happy Hanukkah.
[♪♪♪]
I have a meeting
with a client in Philly,
but you were so evasive
on the phone,
I had to stop by and see you.
Imagine my surprise
when I find out
that I'm already here.
Yeah, I'm sorry, Ethan...
and incredibly embarrassed.
I'm just trying to process this.
How did the other Ethan happen?
His name is Joel Parker.
I met him at Megan and Larry's
Friendsmas party.
He's an actor.
So you hired an actor
to pretend that they were me?
Yeah.
I know it sounds crazy.
I just...
I was so tired of coming home
alone for the holidays,
and...
I wanted Whispering Pines
to see me
with my very own holiday date.
I get it, but that's extreme.
I know,
and I have made
such a mess of this,
and now I've involved
my parents and Joel...
and they really like him.
So do I.
Exactly what is
your relationship?
We're just friends.
You sure about that?
'Cause I hate
how things ended like that.
I just thought maybe we could...
Ethan.
You were right about us.
We're not meant to be together.
I'm really sorry
I got you into this.
No, no.
It was my fault...
The way things ended,
right before the holidays.
I hope you have
a really nice Christmas.
I'll be working through it.
Well, I hope that goes well.
You're a really special
person, okay?
You deserve the best.
And stop worrying
about what other people
think about you.
This is a way better goodbye
than the last one.
- I'll drop you off.
- Okay.
I'm starting to worry here.
You haven't heard
anything about the movie?
I will let you know
as soon as I do.
Any other auditions out there?
No, no.
Everything's shut down,
including myself...
but maybe after the holidays.
How's it going out there?
The research is helpful.
I feel like I have
some sense of the character.
Yes! Yes! This is what
we were talking about.
Dig in. We're going
to get paid for acting.
Amazing.
So, listen,
Megan is as curious as I am...
how's it going with Brooke?
It's going okay.
I didn't expect it
to mean so much to me.
Yeah. Thanks for the update.
- Keep me posted.
- [call disconnects]
Joel?
[Glen] Ethan,
you got to come outside
and check out
this snowman we're building.
Maybe later.
Oh, is everything okay?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
Just business.
Okay, I see
what's going on here.
Year-end filings, right?
I get it.
I'm an accountant.
I played an accountant once.
- Pardon?
- What?
What?
Tessa,
the marshmallows are ready!
Hey, I just left Ethan inside.
Something's going on.
He seems kind of off.
Do you think they had a fight?
I don't know.
Maybe you should talk to Brooke.
Okay.
So glad that we don't fight.
Those look good.
Very warm!
Hey.
Hi.
Is everything okay
with you and Ethan?
Yeah. Why do you ask?
Just relationships
can be complicated...
especially during the holidays.
Incredibly complicated.
Glen and I have
our ups and downs.
You guys seem like
the perfect couple.
There's no such thing.
The house is costing too much,
and we work too many hours,
taking time away from Tessa.
It all takes its toll.
So I'm living in your shadow
and you have clay feet?
I am mixing my metaphors,
but I think you know
what I'm saying.
I have problems
like everyone else.
I'm just better at hiding mine.
And now you are being
wise and caring.
How am I supposed
to live up to that?
You're coming into your own.
I crunch numbers all day...
and you're so creative...
and now you have
this amazing guy.
That was a compliment.
Why the frown?
There's something
I need to tell you.
It's the first night of Hanukkah
and Ethan says
I get to light the Menorah.
That's great, Tessa.
Come on.
What do you need to tell me?
Oh, just that it's
the first night of Hanukkah.
Come on, it's candle time.
Okay.
Hey.
It's almost time
to light the candles.
What's wrong?
You have a really nice family.
Yeah.
And a really nice boyfriend.
Yeah, I'm...
I'm glad that worked out.
I meant you, not Ethan.
I was downtown.
I saw you guys.
Joel...
it's not what you think.
We were saying goodbye for good.
I was never in love with Ethan.
I was just in love
with the idea of him.
And what's your idea of me?
That you're funny,
and caring,
and you really,
really like the holidays.
I just...
wish you could be you.
Yeah, well,
that's my idea of you.
Funny, I can barely
tell us apart.
I am... I'm an actor.
I know who I am.
I'm noticing
that this conversation
is all about you, Mr. Actor.
Really?
Your town, your family,
your boyfriend...
and it's all about me, huh?
Oh, it's on!
It's fun being you and me.
Yeah. It really is.
And just when you thought
it couldn't get
any more complicated.
And then it does.
Oh, you are going to get it!
[Joel] ♪ Barukh atah Adonai ♪
♪ Eloheinu Melekh ha'olam ♪
♪ Asher kid'shanu b'mitzvotav ♪
♪ V'tzivanu l'hadlik ner
shel Hanukkah ♪
This is such a nice tradition.
May love and light
fill your heart
this joyous season.
Amen.
Does this mean
we get to open presents now?
[laughing]
I think it does.
Do you want to go find one?
Yeah? Okay.
[♪♪♪]
♪ I have a little dreidel ♪
♪ I made it out of clay ♪
♪ And when it's dry and ready ♪
♪ A dreidel I will play ♪
♪ Oh, dreidel, dreidel
dreidel ♪
♪ I made it out of clay ♪
♪ And when it's dry and ready ♪
♪ A dreidel I will play ♪
♪ Hey! ♪
Okay...
Oops.
My dreideling needs some work.
It's all in the wrist.
Show-off.
What did you get?
Shin.
More gelt.
Guilt?
Not that kind of guilt.
Gelt.
Chocolate coins covered in gold.
That makes sense.
Tessa, you are up.
Gimmel!
I think Hanukkah rocks.
I do, too.
This is
what Emily's mother wears.
Brooke, I can't believe
you made this.
Thanks.
We are having so much fun.
I just wish we could include
Ethan's family.
Oh, yeah, they went away
for the holidays.
- Why don't I just call?
- No.
Well, you can't...
because they went on a cruise.
Oh.
[telephone rings]
That's nice.
Hello...
Why?
Okay, yeah, I'll let Tessa know.
Roger just canceled
the rehearsal.
I still need
to fit all of the costumes.
Connecticut must be beautiful
this time of year.
Yeah, yeah.
All the trees, the snow...
How come you're not spending
the holidays with your family?
Brooke wanted us
to come down here
so I could meet you guys.
It's not all that far.
They could maybe
drive down for the day.
Yeah. That'd be great,
but I...
I can't reach them right now.
Why not?
They're out of town.
They're on a safari.
They love to travel.
We have to go to the theater.
[in a raspy voice]
As you can tell,
I can barely be heard.
I'm afraid we're going
to have to call off
the performance tomorrow night.
What?
This is going to break
Tessa's heart.
All those beautiful costumes
you made.
It's okay.
No, it's not.
My first Christmas
won't have an unhappy ending.
Why can't I play the father?
I've been rehearsing with Tessa.
I know all the lines.
But you're an architect.
Do you really think
you can pull it off?
- I can give it a go.
- No.
Mm-mm.
You know,
as far as architects go,
Ethan's a pretty good actor.
Hey, look,
the play is a tradition
as old as the theater...
the show must go on.
Whispering Pines
loves Christmas.
What do we have to lose?
You had me at Christmas.
[♪♪♪]
It's heavier than it looks.
It feels nice out here.
There it is.
[Brooke] Such a perfectionist.
The rehearsal
went great as well.
I loved seeing my costumes
up on that stage.
It was like
my own little fashion show.
Next stop New York
and a runway of your own.
Yeah, I don't know
if I'm cut out for that.
I'm not trendy or flashy.
I just think that fashion
should be timeless.
You should be
a costume designer.
I have thought about it,
but I don't know.
Well, listen,
don't deny your talent
if it's leading you
in that direction.
You know...
maybe all this
happened for a reason.
Yeah, maybe it did.
We should probably get going.
It's almost time
to light the Menorah.
And it's only two days away
from Christmas.
We have traded holidays.
Yeah.
I think they go
pretty well together.
Me too.
Sure is beautiful.
You know I can't get enough
of these Sufganiyot.
What?
You're standing
underneath the mistletoe.
Oh.
Wonder where that came from.
Mom...
[quietly]
Are we going to do this?
[♪♪♪]
Talk about
a Christmas to remember.
How could it get
more romantic than that?
I can't wait to talk
to your mom about the wedding.
When do they get back
from the cruise?
Cruise? I thought you told me
they were on safari.
Yeah, well,
they went on a cruise to Africa,
and now they're there
on a safari.
They're very adventurous.
Yeah.
Well, I left them a voicemail.
I hope that's okay.
You called her?
There's not that many
Reinharts in New Haven.
That is where they're from?
I just wanted
to introduce myself
and wish them a Happy Hanukkah.
Ethan's mom
is going to be so surprised.
Yeah.
♪ We wish you
a Merry Christmas... ♪
- You're on holiday.
- Almost done, almost done.
- Mom, we're almost out of eggs.
- There's more in the fridge.
♪...A Merry Christmas... ♪
♪ And a happy New Year ♪
It's getting better.
I don't know.
- I love you, Dad.
- I love you.
This is as merry
as Christmas gets.
Enough of this.
What's cooking?
[Donna] I am making
potato latkes for Hanukkah.
Look at all this
crispy golden goodness.
When do we eat?
[Joel] Wait, wait.
You have to have
the full effect.
Okay.
Hold this.
There you go.
Applesauce and sour cream.
We've got Christmas in one room
and Hanukkah in the other.
How does a holiday
get better than this, huh?
♪ O Christmas tree
o Christmas tree ♪
♪ How lovely
are your branches ♪
♪ O Christmas tree
o Christmas tree ♪
♪ How lovely
are your branches ♪
♪ Not only green
in summer's heat ♪
♪ But also winter's snow
and sleet ♪
♪ O Christmas tree
O Christmas tree ♪
♪ How lovely
are your branches! ♪
That one was for you.
The Christmas tree.
This is for you.
Aw.
Okay, so you're a bit
taller than Roger,
so I lengthened the sleeves.
What?
You and I have gotten
pretty close.
Yeah.
Yeah, we've become
very good friends.
Friends...
don't kiss like that.
No. No, they don't.
[Ashley] Brooke!
Do you need
any help with the costumes?
Uh...
yeah.
Um...
I pretty much need help
with everything.
Okay.
Sorry. I've got to make a call.
I'll be right back.
Okay.
Honey, would you
grab that for me, please?
Oh, sure.
Is Larry there?
Who's calling?
- It's Joel Parker.
- Oh, hi, Joel!
So, how's it going with Brooke?
I'm just so curious.
I need to talk to him.
I'll be quick.
- Oh, okay. It's Joel.
- Yes.
Thank you.
Hey. Hey, hey. Good.
Listen, I have
some good news for you.
You're still in the running...
although with
some big competition,
but my money's on you...
because you are
a movie star in the making.
I'm an actor, Larry.
Yeah, but to me, you're both.
So... okay.
Yeah. Exciting.
Fingers crossed.
Definitely.
Okay, talk soon. Bye.
Glen.
Yeah?
Shh.
I just heard "Ethan"
on the phone with someone.
He said his name
was Joel Parker.
What?
It's gotta be a mistake.
No, he said he was an actor.
- An actor?
- Yeah.
Oh...
Okay, okay,
let's just do a quick search.
I'm sure it's probably nothing.
That's him.
That's our Ethan.
You mean Joel Parker?
Why would he lie to Brooke?
Yeah, and why pretend
to be an architect?
Walter?
I just...
I just got a call
from Ethan's mom,
and when I brought up
the wedding,
she had no idea
what I was talking about.
Sweetheart,
Ethan is not who he says he is.
What do you mean?
"Oy vey," indeed.
Am I right?
[Walter grumbles]
Brooke's fiancé is a fraud.
Oh, no!
Walter...
She is going to be crushed
when she finds out.
Well, at least
that mystery is solved.
[Walter grumbles]
[Joel sighs]
Hey, what's wrong?
I have to go on tonight,
and all I can think about
is you and me
and how to tell your family
the truth.
Yeah.
I can barely
look them in the eyes.
I hate feeling like this.
Well, there's no good time
to tell them...
it might as well be now.
You've been so kind,
but there's something
you need to know...
That your real name
is Joel Parker?
Why would you lie to us?
Please don't... don't blame Joel.
This is all my fault.
You knew about this?
Wait. Why would you do
something like this?
Because I was tired
of coming home for the holidays
and always being
the only one alone.
You thought
this would be better, hmm?
Listen, I know that...
I know that this sounds crazy...
but when Ethan and I broke up...
So hang on.
There actually is an Ethan?
Yes.
And you all met him.
The other Ethan
is the real Ethan.
I am very disappointed
in both of you.
I'm so sorry, Donna.
I am, too.
[♪♪♪]
[Walter clears his throat]
I am sorry, Walter.
You should be.
That being said...
there's something
I need to know.
How do you really feel
about my daughter?
I care for her.
With all my heart.
How do I know you're not acting?
I'm not that good.
I know.
I just saw your commercial.
I have not forgiven you...
not yet.
I don't blame you.
Yes, well, I am your mother,
and I have a job to do.
What's that?
I have to help you
sort this out.
Honey, how do you
really feel about Joel?
I don't know.
I think you do.
He's everything
I wanted Ethan to be.
And he loves my family.
I think he might love Christmas
more than I do.
So then
what are you so afraid of?
Getting hurt.
I felt the same way
about your father,
and look how that turned out.
I really think this guy
is worth the risk.
Oh, my girl.
Thanks, Mom.
We've been waiting for so long.
Can we open presents now?
Oh, dear, let's just wait
a few more minutes, okay?
He's not coming home, is he?
[Mother] Oh, darling,
don't give up hope.
At the very least,
both of you need to know
your father is here in spirit.
[knocking]
[Mother] You're here!
My wish came true!
I have spent many cold days
and dark nights
wishing to be back
in my family's warm embrace.
It's a Christmas Angel.
I made it for you.
My Christmas angel
is right here in my arms!
Merry Christmas, Father.
And Merry Christmas
to you, my darling girl.
Finally here.
But the ones that I love...
...you are my home...
...and you are my heart.
Can we open presents now?
[laughing]
He is a really great actor.
Yeah.
And he's a really good guy.
Costumes by Brooke Miller!
Yes! That's my daughter!
[applause and cheering]
I cannot thank you enough
for these costumes.
So beautiful.
You look stunning.
You have to keep this.
- [Roger] Brooke?
- Yes?
You have some fans
that wanted to say hello.
Sarah and I go way back...
all the way back
to our summer-stock days.
Oh, wow.
I'll let you talk.
Okay.
Sarah insisted
I join her at this...
quaint provincial production.
And I'm very happy she did.
It was beautiful.
Far exceeded my expectations.
Thank you.
I had no idea
how talented you are.
Your sketches were impressive.
But this...
was stunning.
I would be proud to have you
as part of
my senior design team.
Really?
Wow.
Thank you, but I don't think
that's something I want anymore.
What is it that you want?
To be a costume designer.
Well, you already are.
I suspect we'll be working
together very soon.
I hope so.
Well, there she is!
[cheering]
I really like acting.
You were amazing.
Tessa, you mean
the world to me...
and I really hope
that you can forgive me.
Yeah, I hope you can forgive
both of us.
What do you mean?
Well...
acting is for the stage...
not in real life, and...
I was pretending to be
someone else.
My real name is Joel...
but I want you to know
I meant every word
I said to you.
Well, whatever your name is,
you're okay with me.
Telling the truth
is really important,
and I promise I will
always tell you the truth
from now on, okay?
Is he really your boyfriend?
Yes, he is.
For what it's worth...
I approve.
Thanks, Dad.
For what it's worth...
me too.
Glen.
Okay, we're going
to go home now.
Good idea.
- Come on.
- Hot chocolate!
[phone ringing]
Oh, sorry.
It's okay.
- It's Larry.
- Go.
Hi, Larry.
Hey, Joel.
Listen, I'm sorry.
The director got nervous
and decided to go
with a bigger name.
Well, I...
I won't say I don't care...
but, you know, I...
I think I'm going to be
just fine.
Okay, well, I feel awful.
A week ago, this phone call
would have been a lot harder...
but so much has happened
since then.
Well, I'll take
my cue from you...
if you're okay with it, so am I.
And that's your friend talking,
not your agent.
Happy holidays, Larry.
Happy holidays, Joel.
What did he say?
I didn't get the role.
The director
went with a bigger name.
Well, he's making
a huge mistake.
I didn't realize
how good you are.
You were so moving in the play.
You know,
I didn't get the movie...
but maybe I got the girl.
I want you to have both.
You know, being here
has taught me a lot.
I don't want to take
unforgettable roles
that I don't care about.
I'd rather do community theater
and wait for something
I believe in.
Good for you.
How about you?
What are you going to do
with all your talent?
I'm going to be
a costume designer.
I think it's time
I start following my heart.
You know...
New York's only two hours away.
I could see myself
living here some day.
This Christmas
has brought so many gifts.
How about we go spend
some time with the family?
Okay.
[Brooke]
Your nose is really cold.
[Joel] Yeah.
[♪♪♪]
It smells incredible in here.
I could smell the brisket
all the way down the hallway.
I... I have kind of
an announcement.
Every year,
it's been a tradition
in our family that I...
I carve the Christmas turkey.
This year, I think it's time
to pass the torch.
Glen.
Oh, um...
I've been waiting, like,
15 years for this.
Thanks, Walter.
Dad.
So, Dad, how exactly
do you carve a turkey?
[grumbles]
Tessa, do you like your gifts?
I got this one for Hanukkah
and this one for Christmas.
I love them both.
What about you, Brooke?
What did you get for Christmas?
I already have
everything I need.
Well...
I did get you
a little something.
Happy Hanukkah.
Merry Christmas.
[Brooke]
It's absolutely perfect.
I can't wait for you
to meet my family.
This is nothing.
[laughing]
[♪♪♪]
Come on, everybody.
It's Christmas.
And Hanukkah.
- Let's eat.
- Yes.
RIP-FIXES-SYNC
by VaVooM
♪ I believe in Christmas time ♪
♪ When the world
is a sheet of white ♪
♪ Hear the children singing ♪
♪ Listen to
the sleigh bells chime ♪
♪ How I want you
in my arms tonight ♪
♪ Sitting right by
the fireside... ♪